Guide to the ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
- Series VIII. Correspondence, 1953-1991
  - Congressional Joint Economic Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, proposal and speech re economic revival of the U.S.
  - Congressional Letters [folder 1 of 3], 1974-1986 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    re political support, invitations, legislative issues and related routine from Ted Kennedy, Daniel Moynihan, Hubert Humphrey, Walter Mondale, Robert Abrams, Thomas O'Neill Jr., Jacob Javits, John Glenn, Gary Hart, Alan Cranston, Bill Bradley and others.
  - Congressional Letters [folder 2 of 3], 1974-1986 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Letters [folder 3 of 3], 1974-1986 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Conrail, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Correspondence with senators re opposition of sale of Conrail.
  - Consumer Assembly Dinner, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Correspondence re dinner honoring Chaikin.
  - Consumer Complaints, 1979-1983 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Complaints from consumers re workmanship in garments purchased.
  - Consumer Report, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Form letter, mailing list and report.
  - Contract Negotiations, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Contracts, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Sample independent agreement sent to all Regional Directors.
  - Contributions, 1974-1984 (Box 25, Folder 17-26)
    Correspondence re contributions made and requests for contributions from organizations.
  - Contributions [folder 1 of 5], 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Related routine correspondence re contributions by ILGWU
  - Contributions [folder 2 of 5], 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Contributions [folder 3 of 5], 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Contributions [folder 4 of 5], 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Contributions [folder 5 of 5], 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Convention, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Correspondence re arrangements, invitations, convention call; press information packet and program.
  - Convention, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Letters of congratulations on Chaikin`s re- election and other miscellaneous documents.
  - Convention, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Invitations for convention speakers; background documents.
  - Conventions. Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Housing, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Correspondence and legal documents re discrimination against Blacks and Hispanics and related routine.
  - Cornell University, 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    re NYSSILR programs/workshop information; arrangements for speeches, etc.
  - Costa Rica, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Council for Revitalization of Employment and Industry in Philadelphia, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Correspondence re new garment center in Philadelphia; attacks on the programs of the Garment Center and related routine.
  - Council on Foreign Relations [folder 1 of 2], 1979-1986 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    (Chaikin, member) Correspondence re activities, conferences and meetings on U.S.-Japan labor issues, industrial policy, trade with China, world economy and others.
  - Council on Foreign Relations [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1986 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Council on International Business (N.Y.S. Governor's Council), 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    (Chaikin, member) Correspondence re New York State economic problems and related routine.
  - Country Miss, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    re strike at Glasgow Mfg. Company (Kentucky) and request for arbitration.
  - Cowden, Marc, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Crabb, Charles R. Jr., 1982 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Culpeper Foundation, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Cuomo, Mario, 1982-1986 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Thanking Chaikin for his political support; invitation to Cuomo's inauguration; re appointments to the State Job Training Partnership Council; re closing Empire State College; funding of ILG's Occupational Alcoholism Project; staff reductions in Division of Labor Standards; Bd. of Advisors of the Friends of Mario Cuomo Committee; limitation on imports of textiles and apparels; funding of community colleges; sale of Conrail and other related routine.
  - D.C. Friends of Ireland (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Undated. Related routine
  - Dalrymple Associates, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Daniels, Wilbur [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    re Jane Fonda's promotion of the ILGWU label; financial condition of Local 40; partial transcript of PBS McNeil/Lehrer Report on which Chaikin was guest re ILG representatives who walked out of Geneva talks; documents re request for approval of special withdrawal liability rules; re shop closings; correspondence re Koret-Levi Strauss negotiations and non-union work; financial problems at Bobbie Brooks plants and request for changes in contract; and related routine.
  - Daniels, Wilbur [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Dary Sue Fashions, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Several grievances against Dary Sue. work given to non-union firms, and excessive imports; paid $175,000 to Local 23-25 for violations.
  - Daugherty, Thomas J., 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - David Dubinsky Foundation, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Davis, Ronald, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Deborah Heart and Lung Center, 1973-1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    re support and related routine.
  - Debs, Eugene V. and Meyer London Memorial, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 9a)
    re 50th Anniversary.
  - DeFazio, Hugh E., 1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    re activities and contributions.
  - Democratic Convention, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    re arrangements for Chaikin and others to attend.
  - Democratic National Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    re contributions and party support, meetings, conferences; correspondence re Chaikin's nominating speech at 1980 Convention for Jimmy Carter.
  - Democratic National Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1986 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Party, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Includes Chaikin's speech seconding the nomination of Jimmy Carter and miscellaneous.
  - Direction 80 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    re program at Tulane University of which Chaikin was a participant.
  - Ditchley Foundation, 1977-1982 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Correspondence and arrangements re Conference on Lessons from Japan and related routine.
  - Domanek, Karl A., 1981 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Dorby Frocks, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    re company using non-union contractors.
  - Dress Negotiations [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1982 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    Documents and correspondence re contract talks with manufacturers and letters of congratulations re settlements.
  - Dress Negotiations [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1982 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Drucker, Jack, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Dubinsky, David, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 22a)
    Sympathy letters upon death of Dubinsky.
  - Dubrow, Evelyn, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Durban, Dick, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    re political support of Durban (Illinois).
  - Durkin, Michael, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - East River Housing [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1983 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    Includes correspondence re charges of discrimination, financial matters, minutes of Board of Directors and related routine.
  - East River Housing [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1983 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Easter Seal Telethon, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Eastern Education Consortium, Inc., 1985 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Eban, Abba, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    re request for contribution to the Beit Berl Institute in Israel.
  - Economic Education for Clergy, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Education [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    Correspondence and brochure re conferences on education.
  - Education [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Education. Saddle Rock, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    Letters from elementary school children after Mr. Chaikin had addressed their class.
  - Egypt [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    re visit of first AFL-CIO delegation with Egyptian Trade Union Federation officials. includes correspondence, handwritten diary of Mrs. Chaikin, 8 p. "Briefing Paper For AFL-CIO Delegation to Egypt," and related documents.
  - Egypt [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Employer Associations, 1976-1985 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    Correspondence re imports, wage and hour enforcement in the south and related routine.
  - Energy, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    Includes 3 p. statement by Chaikin and related documents.
  - Ethiopia, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    Correspondence re contributions for Ethiopian relief effort.
  - Euro-Communism, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    Publications re growing power of the European Communist parties.
  - Evan-Picone, 1981-1986 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    re use of non- ILG contractors.
  - Evans, Lois, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Export-Import Bank of the U.S., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - FDR-Four Freedom Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - FFACT (Fiber, Fabric and Apparel Coalition for Trade) [folder 1 of 3], 1985 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Correspondence and releases re Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act of 1985; draft copy (173 p.), "The Textile Trade Crisis."
  - FFACT (Fiber, Fabric and Apparel Coalition for Trade) [folder 2 of 3], 1985 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - FFACT (Fiber, Fabric and Apparel Coalition for Trade) [folder 3 of 3], 1985 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Fair Trade Practices, 1971-1983 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    re imports and trade; 5 p. memo to Stulberg (1971) "to plan a massive national campaign," regarding the problem of imports.
  - Fairfield University, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    re Committee on Evolutionary American Capitalism
  - Farmworker Justice Fund, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    (Chaikin, member, Advisory Board) Related routine.
  - Fashion Capital, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 1 of 6], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    (Chaikin, member, Board of Trustees) re activities of the Institute. correspondence, minutes, and related documents; 195 p. "The Fashion Institute of Technology; An Overview," (1981?).
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 2 of 6], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 3 of 6], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 4 of 6], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 5 of 6], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology [folder 6 of 6], 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Federacion Interamericana de Trabajadores, 1982-1986 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Federal Election Commission, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Apparel Manufacturers, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Feldman, Matthew, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Fickling and Walker, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Field Foundation, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Five Hundred (500) Club [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Re aid for political candidates, ILGWU political fund raising efforts.
  - Five Hundred (500) Club [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Florida International University, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Food, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    Re food prices (legislation, etc.)
  - Ford Foundation [folder 1 of 3], 1984-1988 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    (Chaikin, Member Executive Panel) Re Project on Social Welfare Policy and the American Future. Includes agenda booklet, correspondence, reports, papers, notes concerning the project, "The Future of the Welfare State."
  - Ford Foundation [folder 2 of 3], 1984-1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Ford Foundation [folder 3 of 3], 1984-1988 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Foreign Affairs Article, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Correspondence re article Chaikin wrote for Foreign Affairs entitled "Trade, Foreign Investment and Deindustralization: A Labor Perspective."
  - Foreign. Brazil, 1977-1980 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Re trade relations and Brazilian trade union movement.
  - Foreign. Chile [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1979 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    Re Chaikin press conference in Chile during solidarity visit by AFL-CIO delegation to Chile; "Labor and Human Rights: A Chilean Chronicle" by Rosalind Chaikin and related documents.
  - Foreign. Chile [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1979 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Foreign. France, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Foreign. General, 1975-1982 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    Miscellaneous papers.
  - Foreign. Germany, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Includes 10 p. memorandum re the 11th DGB Congress and related issues.
  - Foreign. Israel, 1978-1984 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    From Yerucham Meshel, Secretary-General, General Federation of Labour in Israel re serious labour problems.
  - Foreign. Italy, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Foreign. Japan (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Foreign. Poland, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Foreign. South Africa [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    Includes reports, remarks, correspondence re AFL-CIO delegation to South Africa; information re Southern African Workshop at Yale University in which Chaikin participated and 27 p. speech by Chaikin; 11 p. acceptance speech by Mangosuthu Buthelezi (Chairman of South African Black Alliance) upon receipt of 1982 George Meany Human Rights Award.
  - Foreign. South Africa [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Form Letters, 1976-1981 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Fraternal Greetings, 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    Copies of letters sent by Chaikin to international union officers and delegates during their conventions.
  - Free General Workers Union (USSR), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Free Trade Union Institute, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Includes minutes, reports and related documents.
  - Freedom House, 1975-1990 (Box 29, Folder 2a)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Trustees) re fund raising, projects and activities and related documents.
  - Freeman, Orville, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Freeport Minerals Company, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - French-American Foundation, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Frontlash, 1978-1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Full Employment Action Council, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Fund For A Democratic Majority, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    3 p. letter from Senator Ted Kennedy asking Chaikin to join him at his home for a fund-raising dinner for the Fund; discusses '84 election and other issues and concerns.
  - Fund Raisers, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Lists of names for reception for Bill Bradley and Ted Kennedy; lists for private luncheon at the 500 Club; lists for Bess Myerson breakfast and Daniel Moynihan dinner.
  - Future Textiles, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Futures Group, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Correspondence and publication re study of the future U.S. workforce.
  - Garment Center Economic Security Council, Inc., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Garment Industry Productivity Seminar, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Garment Worker, The, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Re dedication of 8 foot sculpture of "The Garment Worker" as a Fashion Avenue landmark. includes guest lists, releases, photos, fund-raising letters and lists.
  - Geissler, Anne-Marie, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - General Advisory Council, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    Re 1983 convention decision to create a GAC; includes letters of recommendation and lists of names.
  - General Federation of Labor In Israel, 1971-1987 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Letters of thanks from members after U.S. visit.
  - General Knit of California, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Re Japanese-U.S. venture. letter to President of the company re unionizing of plant from outset.
  - General Office and Industry, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    6 p. pamphlet, "On the Possibility of Developing Closer Ties to the Mexican Labor Movement," a report to Sol Chaikin by Cornelius Wall of Western States Region; plans for export promotion program; and miscellaneous.
  - Geneva (Multilateral Trade Negotiations), 1978 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    Re Chaikin's visit to Geneva.
  - Germany, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Governor's Task Force on Housing, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    (Chaikin, Member) Related routine.
  - Graham, Betty, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Grants (Box 29, Folder 25)
    Undated. Includes handwritten lists.
  - Green Dolmatch Inc., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    Re advertising.
  - Greenstone, Ellen S., 1980 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Grossberg, Israel, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Haber, William, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Hammond, R.E. (Box 29, Folder 30)
    Undated. Concern of members of Knitgood Workers Union, Local 155 re wages for piece workers.
  - Hartman, Arthur, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Hartman, David, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    Letter thanking Chaikin for his appearance on "Good Morning America."
  - Harvard University [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1988 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    Correspondence re participating in class lectures; correspondence re survey by researchers at the Harvard School of Public Health concerned with problems of the upper limb in women garment workers; 43 p. paper, "The Two Faces of Unionism", by R.B. Freeman and J.L. Medoff of Harvard; workshops and conference participation and related routine.
  - Harvard University [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1988 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Harve-Benard, Ltd., 1985 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    Re liquidated damage claim.
  - Haun, Karen, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Hearst Foundation, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    Re Chaikin's nomination as an Honorary Alumnus of the University.
  - Helsinki Watch (Madrid) [folder 1 of 5], 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    Correspondence and documents re appeal of Yuri Orlov; Baltic World Conference memo re Soviet Aggression; statements and remarks by Max Kampleman,co-chairman of Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe; list of "Imprisoned Members of the Helsinki Monitoring Groups"; "Briefing Book for the Public Members of the U.S. Delegation to the Madrid Meeting"; 18 p. unedited, informal report by Andrzej Korbonski (Univ. of Calif.) entitled, "Poland: July 1979"; President Carter's remarks at ceremony commemorating the 5th Anniversary of the Helsinki Accords; petitions and protests sent to Polish authorities to free political prisoners.
  - Helsinki Watch (Madrid) [folder 2 of 5], 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    Correspondence and documents re appeal of Yuri Orlov; Baltic World Conference memo re Soviet Aggression; statements and remarks by Max Kampleman, co-chairman of Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe; list of "Imprisoned Members of the Helsinki Monitoring Groups"; "Briefing Book for the Public Members of the U.S. Delegation to the Madrid Meeting"; 18 p. unedited, informal report by Andrzej Korbonski (Univ. of Calif.) entitled, "Poland: July 1979"; President Carter's remarks at ceremony commemorating the 5th Anniversary of the Helsinki Accords; petitions and protests sent to Polish authorities to free political prisoners.
  - Helsinki Watch (Madrid) [folder 3 of 5], 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Helsinki Watch (Madrid) [folder 4 of 5], 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Helsinki Watch (Madrid) [folder 5 of 5], 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Henry Friedricks and Company, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Herman Kay Company, Inc., 1984 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    Re liquidated damage claims.
  - Hertz Corporation, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    Re IRS requirements on leased cars; car rentals; orders and miscellaneous.
  - Hertzog, Chaim. Reception, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Hewitt Associates, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    Re National Retirement Fund financial performance results.
  - High School of Fashion Industries, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Higher Education and Economic Development, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    Chaikin. principal speaker at conference; 15 p. speech by Chaikin, "A Union's Stake in Higher Education."
  - Hispanic Labor Committee, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Histadrut [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1986 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    Correspondence re activities, financial contributions; minutes; dinner program. Humanitarian Award presented to Chaikin; conference plans; Louis Stulberg Hospital Project; difficulties in the Middle East and related routine.
  - Histadrut [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1986 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Histadrut [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1986 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Holiday Pay Fund, 1976-1982 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    Re Holiday Pay Commission Agreement.
  - Hollings, Ernest, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Re political contribution.
  - Holmes, Robert, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Includes program for Testimonial Dinner in Holmes' honor. (Chaikin, guest speaker).
  - Homework, 1981-1985 (Box 30, Folder 3-13)
    Contains substantial amount of correspondence opposing the proposal of the Department of Labor to lift the 40 year ban on industrial homework in the apparel industries. (Includes hundreds of letters from employees, companies and organizations).
  - HRT Industries, Inc., 1984 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Legal document re bankruptcy.
  - Human Rights, 1978-1983 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Correspondence re plans for "Tribute to Hubert Humphrey" dinner by the New York Executive Committee for the HHH Institute.
  - Illegal Aliens, 1975-1983 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    2 p. draft "Policy Statement"; clippings; reports; Department of Justice release; correspondence re legislative efforts dealing with employment problem; Haitian refugees; and other related documents.
  - Immigration [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    ILGWU statement on amnesty, correspondence re immigration reform, factory raids by Immigration Service agents; testimony by Jay Mazur, Vice-President, before Select Committee, (10 p.); "Faces of Immigration: the Cubans of New Jersey," by Philip Dolce, (27 p.); AFL-CIO Resolutions; 2 p. confidential Selection Commission on Immigration and Refugee Policy memo re highlights of findings on illegal immigrants, 1/23/80; and other related documents.
  - Immigration [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1985 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Import Bill [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Correspondence with congressmen re the Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act; statement on Act from Federation of Korean Textile Workers Unions and related documents.
  - Import Bill [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Import Bill, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Import Coalition [folder 1 of 4], 1971-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Re "Crafted With Pride In U.S.A." program of the American, Fibre, Textile, Apparel Coalition; 50 p. "Background Data on Imports, Textile and Apparel Industries and Their Workers" by Research Department of the ILGWU; correspondence re joint campaign efforts on imports with Amalgamated Clothing Workers; strengthening the U.S. Customs Service enforcement of apparel import restraints; recommendations to the White House Working Group on Textiles; correspondence re imports rollback campaign; 5 p. memo to President Stulberg from Chaikin (1971) re planning a massive national campaign against imports.
  - Import Coalition [folder 2 of 4], 1971-1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Import Coalition [folder 3 of 4], 1971-1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Import Coalition [folder 4 of 4], 1971-1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Imports, 1978-1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Imports. 807 Program, 1976-1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Correspondence and related documents re the repeal of Item 807 of the Tariff Schedules.
  - Imports. Multifiber Arrangement, 1977-1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Correspondence and related documents re re-negotiation of MFA.
  - Imports. Rollback Campaign, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)